{
    "title": "Example Quiz 2",
    "marking-occurs": "at-quiz-end",
    "rounds": [{
        "name": "Setup",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Enter your name:",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Any"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Cocktail Round üç∏",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Which cocktail is made with vodka, triple sec, cranberry juice, and freshly squeezed or sweetened lime juice?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Cosmopolitan"
        }, {
            "question": "Which cocktail consists of tequila, orange liqueur, and lime juice often served with salt on the rim of the glass?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Margarita"
        }, {
            "question": "Which cocktail is made from gin, lemon juice, sugar, and carbonated water?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Tom Collins"
        }, {
            "question": "Which mixed drink is made with bourbon, lemon juice, a teaspoon of sugar, and an optional egg white?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Whiskey Sour"
        }, {
            "question": "Which traditional Cuban highball consists of white rum, lime juice, sugar, soda water, and mint?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Mojito"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the name of the cocktail made with gin, vodka, white Lillet, Angostura bitters and lemon zest that James Bond invents in Casino Royale?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Vesper"
        }, {
            "question": "What flavour is Chambord liquor?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Raspberry"
        }, {
            "question": "Which key ingredient is missing for a Long Island Ice Tea - Gin, Vodka, White Rum, Cointreau, Lemon Juice, Dash of Cola, Lemon Wedge?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Tequila"
        }, {
            "question": "Which cocktail is vodka and coffee liqueur?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Black Russian"
        }, {
            "question": "What would you call a beer cocktail made from Guinness and Champagne?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Black Velvet"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "London Round üá¨üáß",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Who became Mayor of London in May 2016?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Sadiq Khan"
        }, {
            "question": "Opened in 1987, what does the acronym DLR stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Docklands Light Railway"
        }, {
            "question": "Opened in 1979, which is the newest line on the London Underground network?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Jubilee"
        }, {
            "question": "Which Second World War museum ship is permanently moored on the River Thames?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "HMS Belfast"
        }, {
            "question": "The Shaftesbury Memorial Fountain is located at the southeastern side of which public space?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Picadilly Circus"
        }, {
            "question": "The Theatre Royal, in Covent Garden, backs onto which street?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Drury Lane"
        }, {
            "question": "Which area of London is believed to derive its name from a former hunting cry?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Soho"
        }, {
            "question": "Where is the burial place of Michael Faraday, John Galsworthy and author Douglas Adams?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Highgate Cemetery"
        }, {
            "question": "Which London park is famous for its Speakers' Corner?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Hyde Park"
        }, {
            "question": "Name the large area off Whitehall which is the site of the annual Trooping the Colour?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Horse Guards Parade"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "iPhone Round üì±",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Which iPhone model was released in the color bright green?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "iPhone 5C"
        }, {
            "question": "Which was the first iPhone model to use Lightning cables?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "iPhone 5"
        }, {
            "question": "Which was the first iPhone model released in gold?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "iPhone 5S"
        }, {
            "question": "What version of the iPhone's OS introduced cut-and-paste functionality?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "3"
        }, {
            "question": "What codename did Apple employees use to the iPhone before it was announced?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Project Purple"
        }, {
            "question": "Which model of iPhone was the first to have Touch ID?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "iPhone 5S"
        }, {
            "question": " The Digital Rights Management system on the iPhone was broken by a group of hackers, which allowed for other non-Apple applications to be installed onto the devices. By what name is such a cracking of Digital Rights Management better-known?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Jailbreak"
        }, {
            "question": "A similar handheld device is also available from Apple that has most features that the iPhone has, minus the telephone. What is the name of this device?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": " iPod Touch"
        }, {
            "question": "What major new feature was introduced in the iPhone X?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Face ID"
        }, {
            "question": "Who portrayed the Apple CEO in the 2015 movie Steve Jobs?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Michael Fassbender"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Sci-Fi Round üëΩ",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Which popular TV show had characters named Fox Mulder and Dana Scully?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "The X-Files"
        }, {
            "question": "Captain James Kirk is the most famous Captain of the USS Enterprise in Star Trek ‚Äì but who had the job before him in the TV series?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Captain Christopher Pike"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the superhero alter-ego of the character Billy Batson?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Shazam"
        }, {
            "question": "In Game of Thrones, what is the name of Westeros‚Äô capital city?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "King‚Äôs Landing"
        }, {
            "question": "Which superhero is both a Marvel and a DC character?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Captain Marvel"
        }, {
            "question": "What exactly is Deep Space Nine in the television series Star Trek: Deep Space Nine?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Spacestation"
        }, {
            "question": "In the Alien movie series, what is the name of Ellen Ripley‚Äôs pet cat?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Jonesy"
        }, {
            "question": "Robin is the sidekick to DC's Batman, but what is his true name?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Dick Grayson"
        }, {
            "question": "Where were Peter Jackson‚Äôs Lord of the Rings movies filmed?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "New Zealand"
        }, {
            "question": "Complete the following famous quote from the TV series Lost in Space: ‚ÄúDanger ____ _____.‚Äù",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Will Robinson"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Technology Round ü§ñ",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
        }, {
            "question": "One loop inside the body of another loop is called ",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Nested"
        }, {
            "question": "In C what command is used to output text to the console?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Cout"
        }, {
            "question": "What technology is used to record cryptocurrency transactions?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Blockchain"
        }, {
            "question": "What kind of malware is designed to take advantage of a security hole before it is known?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Zero-day exploit"
        }, {
            "question": "What does acronym FOSS stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Free and Open-Source Software"
        }, {
            "question": "What technology is used to make telephone calls over the Internet possible?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "VoIP"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the term for text that automatically continues from one line to the next?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Word wrapping"
        }, {
            "question": "IMAX is a contraction of which words?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Image Maximum"
        }]
    }]
}
